#### Personal Information

# **Golam Mostafa**

- 32, South Mugda, Dhaka, 1214 (Bangladesh)
- **(**+880) 1843 666660
- imsaifun@gmail.com
- sporsho9

### Personal Statement

I'm a Front-end developer with more than 8 years of experience in the software industry, specialized in writing light-weight css, animation, SVG and **ReactJS**. My ambition is improving or writing scalable, secure & maintainable application.

#### Personal Skills

Languages :	JavaScript (ES 6+), TypeScript
Library & Frameworks :	React JS(Hooks, Context API, Router), <b>Next Js</b> , Antd, Chakra
State Management :	Redux
Database Management:	MongoDB
API:	Rest API, GraphQL
Testing Tools:	Jest
Style & Library:	CSS <b>Flex</b> , <b>SCSS</b> , <b>Bootstrap</b> , Tailwind, Material UI, Bulma
Version Control :	Git with Smart Git Flow; used with <b>Github</b> , Gitlab.
Development Tools :	Gulp,NPM, Yarn, Postman, Insomnia, JWT, Firebase, Vercel
SCRUM/Agile :	Completed CSM Training and practising SCRUM methodology at work.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present

Full Stack Developer

Author, Codecanyon Marketplace.

Website: https://codecanyon.net/item/pitza-full-stack-react-nextjs-single-restaurant-pizza-order-and-delivery-app/38884828

*Note:* All templates design and developed by me\*

2019 - Present

React/Nextjs Developer

Author, Themeforest Marketplace.

Website: https://themeforest.net/user/imsaifun/portfolio

Note: All templates design and developed by me\*

2015 - 2019

Front End Designer & Developer *Author, Themeforest Marketplace.* 

Website: https://saifun.vercel.app

Note: All templates design and developed by me\*

### **EDUCATION**

Oct 2008 - March 2013

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)

Major in Human Resource Management

International Islamic University Chittagong

## LINKS

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/imsaifun/

Github

https://github.com/imsaifun

Portfolio

https://saifun.vercel.app/